omegabiotek.com 2019-07-03

# Privacy Policy | Omega Bio-tek

Privacy Statement

Omega Bio-tek, Inc. is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Omega Bio-tek, Inc. website and governs data collection and usage. By using the Omega Bio-tek, Inc. website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

Collection of your Personal Information

Omega Bio-tek, Inc. collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. Omega Bio-teks, Inc. also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, preferences, interests, and favorites.

There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Omega Bio-tek, Inc.This information can include your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used by Omega Bio-tek, Inc. for the operation of the service, to maintain the quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Omega Bio-tek, Inc. website.

Omega Bio-tek, Inc. encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from Omega Bio-tek, Inc. so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. Omega Bio-tek, Inc. is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the Omega Bio-tek, Inc. and Omega Bio-tek, Inc. family of websites.

Personal data collected online may also be combined with information you provide Omega Bio-tek, Inc. through other sources such as product registration, call centers or public events such as trade shows or seminars.

Personal data given to Omega Bio-tek, Inc. may be transferred across state and country borders for the purposes of data consolidation, storage, and simplified customer information management.

Use of your Personal Information

Omega Bio-tek, Inc. collects and uses your personal information to operate the Omega Bio-tek, Inc. website and deliver the services you have requested. Omega Bio-tek, Inc. also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Omega Bio-tek, Inc. Omega Bio-tek, Inc. may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

Omega Bio-tek, Inc. does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Omega Bio-tek, Inc. may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Omega Bio-tek, Inc., and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

Omega Bio-tek, Inc. does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.

Omega Bio-tek, Inc. keeps track of the websites and pages our customers visit within Omega Bio-tek, Inc., in order to determine what Omega Bio-tek, Inc. services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Omega Bio-tek, Inc. to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

Omega Bio-tek, Inc. websites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Omega Bio-tek, Inc. or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Omega Bio-tek, Inc.; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Omega Bio-tek, Inc., or the public.

Use of Cookies

The Omega Bio-tek, Inc. website uses “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Omega Bio-tek, Inc. pages, or register with Omega Bio-tek, Inc. site or services, a cookie helps Omega Bio-tek, Inc. to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Omega Bio-tek, Inc. website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Omega Bio-tek, Inc. features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Omega Bio-tek, Inc. services or websites you visit.

Security of your Personal Information

Omega Bio-tek, Inc. secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Omega Bio-tek, Inc. secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to our online financial institution, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

Changes to this Statement

Omega Bio-tek, Inc. will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Omega Bio-tek, Inc. encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Omega Bio-tek, Inc. is protecting your information.

Contact Information

Omega Bio-tek, Inc. welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Omega Bio-tek, Inc. has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Omega Bio-tek, Inc. at info@omegabiotek.com. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
